https://corporate.pirelli.com/corporate/en-ww/sustainability/policies/sust-global-personal-data-protection-policy

Sustainability
At a glancePirelli's modelOrganizational structureMain performance indicatorsSustainability targetsMulti-stakeholder approachStakeholder engagementStakeholder identification and management guidelinesMateriality analysisMain sustainability policiesThe ethical codeCode of conductAnti-corruption programSocial responsibility policy for occupational health, safety and rights, and environmentGlobal human rights policyHealth, safety and environment policyProduct stewardship policyQuality policyGreen sourcing policyEqual opportunities statementWhistleblowing policyPolicy corporate lobbyingGlobal tax policyGlobal personal data protection policyAntitrust programGlobal antitrust and fair competition policyIntellectual property policySustainable natural rubberPirelli social mediaCertification and management standardsReportsSustainability ChannelContact usArchiveFaq
Sustainability
Main sustainability policiesGlobal personal data protection policy
On March 31, 2015 the Board of Directors of Pirelli & C. S.p.A. approved the Policy ” Global Personal Data protection”. The Policy provides information regarding the basic principles of conduct to be followed in the processing of personal data; the policy is directed, in particular, towards directors, employees and all those who represent the company to third parties and that, in the course of its business activities, perform the processing of personal data.
English Version (85,8 KB)
Italian Version (88,2 KB)
German Version (202 KB)
Falkland Islands (Malvinas)
Holy See (Vatican City State)
Virgin Islands, U.S.
I wish to receive direct marketing e-mails/communications in accordance with the Privacy Policy.
I agree to the processing of my personal data for the
purposes of allowing Pirelli and other companies within
the Pirelli group to inform me about future product
offers or promotional activities.
I agree to the transfer of my personal data to
commercial partners of Pirelli for them to inform me
about their future product offers or promotional
activities.
Thank you for contacting us
